Good morning guys, and welcome to this week's video.
I am quite excited because I'm going to be filming a what I eat in a week.
I haven't made one of these before, but I love to watch them myself because you get a bunch of recipe inspiration.
So yesterday I sat down in my computer and I planned out the week what I'm going to be eating.
And we went to the supermarket, and I have never ever bought as much groceries in my life.
And the reason for that is because we just moved into our new place here in Sydney, and there is no supermarket close
by.
So it takes us 30 minutes to walk to the supermarket, and we even brought like a stroller with us.
It's like a specific stroller to carry your groceries.
I've always wanted to buy groceries for the whole week instead of going to the supermarket almost every single day like we usually do.
So I felt like this was the perfect opportunity to plan and prep for the whole week.
And today it's Monday, so I wanted to pick up the camera so I can document everything that I will be making in
this kitchen.
But first, I'm going to show you guys all of the groceries that we bought yesterday.
Okay, this took me a minute because we had already put everything into, you know, the cabinets.
But I really wanted to show you guys, so we have a lot of fruits and veggies.
We bought a bunch of Avocados because they are so delicious.
And then some eggs, of course.
Some protein, we have ground beef and chicken.
And then for dairy, we have some feta, some butter, cottage cheese, and Greek yogurt.
Some more vegetables and herbs.
And then over here, we have a mix of some different things.
We have some coconut water, coconut milk, some beans, olive oil, chicken stock, pasta.
We have some peanut butter, cashew butter, sauerkraut.
And then they had a little snack bar.
And these are chocolate covered almonds.
And yeah, that's about it.
I just put everything back into the cabinets and the refrigerator.
And now it's time to make some breakfast.
And I wanted to make something quite simple because we wanted to go out for a run.
So I have some Greek yogurt that looks like Ben and Jerry's, don't you think?
And I just wanted to make a quick little yogurt bowl with some granola and some berries.
We also bought some organic frozen blueberries and some sourdough rye bread, and I think I'm going to make a little compote
with some berries to put in the yogurt bowl.
I added some cashew butter and some hemp seeds for a little garnish.
I
am making omelette today, and it's not just a regular
omelette because this one has a zucchini.
I usually never cook anything with zucchini, but I saw this recipe online and I thought why not try it out, and I'm not gonna give
any spoilers, but it was really, really good, and it's super easy to make.
I also made electrolytes drink with some coconut water, lime juice, some salt, and water.
It's my go-to drink at the moment, and to spice up my omelette, I added some sriracha and parmesan.
It's time to taste the zucchini omelette.
I am so excited because I am very hungry.
Okay, yum.
It's a bit spicy, and it's actually quite simple to make.
It's
time to make dinner, and I will, by the way, link some of these recipes down below so it's easy for you guys to find them.
On today's menu, we are making lemon chicken orzo soup, and I am very excited to try this one out.
I love soups, and chicken soups especially with some orzo.
I think it's going to be amazing.
So we are going to need some celery and carrots, and of course some chicken, and I bought some organic chicken breasts.
I've been trying to buy more organic, and the pasta, and I tried to find orzo, but they didn't have it.
This was the closest one I could find, and I hope it's going to be similar.
Thank you.
Okay guys, moment of truth!
Okay, yum.
This reminds me of like the alphabet soup you would like eat when you were younger.
Is that a good thing or a bad thing?
I think it's a good thing.
It's like a comfort.
I mean, but elevated with more veggies.
Oh my, this is really, really good.
For breakfast.
Today, we are making protein pancakes.
And these are super simple to make.
You only need a banana, an egg, and some protein powder.
I'm going to double my recipe because I'm also making for Helge.
So I'm going to be mashing two bananas into my bowl.
The weather is really nice, so we decided to eat our breakfast out on the balcony.
And I'm so excited to eat this stack of pancakes.
I added some blueberries and Greek yogurt, and I think it's going to be really good.
I'm going to go on a little walk, get some steps in, get some fresh air and some sun, and I'm going to bring my journal with me
in case if I want to sit down, maybe buy some coffee, and write in my journal.
That's one of my New Year's resolutions.
I feel like I always want to start writing more in my journal, but this year I'm going to make it happen.
For
lunch, I'm making a sweet potato chickpea salad.
So I'm starting by cutting my sweet potato into cubes and adding some seasoning and olive oil.
And I'm adding two cans of chickpeas on a baking tray with some olive oil, lots of seasoning.
Moving on to my kale, I'm giving it a good massage, and I highly recommend doing the same because it makes such a big difference.
Apparently, it breaks down the tough fibers, which makes it easier to digest and also enhances the flavor.
These chickpeas are so addicting.
They're so crispy.
I'm just waiting for the quinoa to be ready so I can assemble the salad, but I just keep on snacking on these.
Look
at
all of these beautiful colors.
This salad is really good.
You could easily make a dressing with some tahini and olive oil and stuff, but I don't have any tahini.
I forgot to buy it.
But I massaged the kale with vinegar, lemon, and all kinds of goodness.
So I feel like it doesn't really need any dressing because the salad is already very flavorful and yummy.
I'm just watching some YouTube videos while eating my salad.
And later this evening, we are actually gonna have dinner with our friends Rob and Selena.
We're going to an Italian restaurant, and I think we are gonna go pretty early because we wanted to have a little stroll in the city and
maybe shoot some Instagram pictures.
Good
morning, guys.
I am having breakfast, and yesterday I meal prepped some chia pudding.
Super simple and convenient if you are on the go and just want to have something quick for breakfast.
It's basically chia seeds, and I put some coconut milk, protein powder, vanilla extract, and a little bit of maple syrup for a bit of sweetness.
And then I just shake the jar to make sure everything is blended together.
And I put it into the fridge overnight, and the next day it's ready to enjoy.
I have these delicious nectarines that I'm gonna slice on top of my chia pudding.
Breakfast is served.
I had some leftover coconut cream, so I added a little bit of that, and I sprinkled some hemp seeds and a little bit of
raw honey, and I not kidding, guys, this is actually really good.
I haven't tried many variations of different fruits.
We tried with some strawberries some time ago, and I didn't like that as much, but with the nectarines and the raw honey, I don't
know, like the combination is really good.
Mmm.
I
am
quite excited to share with you guys today's lunch recipe.
So it's butter beans and cherry tomatoes and, of course, some garlic that I'm gonna heat in a pan, and then we put it on toast
with some cottage cheese and basilica and olive oil, and it is incredible.
I hope you guys will try this out.
While I'm making lunch, Helge went to a cafe to buy some coffee because we don't have a coffee machine in this apartment, which is so
tragic because I love my coffee.
And when we rented out this apartment, we thought there would be a coffee machine because the lady sent pictures of the kitchen, and there was a coffee
machine there, but I had a weird feeling, so I texted her before we were about to move in, and she told me that it broke the same
morning, and apparently it's at the repair shop, but I'm not very optimistic somehow.
I don't know if we would need to.
Buy a French press or a mocha pot or something so we can make some coffee while we're here, but yeah.
For now, we've just been going to this cafe.
It takes about 10 or 13 minutes to walk there, but the coffee is really good, so it's actually worth it.
Helge is here with coffee!
Good?
Very fresh because of the tomatoes and the beans are so good.
There is a thunderstorm outside and lots of lightnings going off.
This is something that Helge and I are not very used to.
In Iceland, we barely get any thunderstorms.
We are making some dinner, or at least Helge is making dinner and I'm on snack duty.
I'm making my all-time favorite snack: medjool dates with some peanut butter, and I'm gonna put some
dark chocolate and put it in the fridge, and it's the best thing in the world.
Oh, looks so good!
What are you making tonight?
I'm making a taco bowl.
It's very easy to make, easy to assemble, high in protein, hopefully delicious as well, so yeah, I'm excited.
Okay
guys, this is so yummy.
It's been a while since we made a taco bowl, but it just reminded me that we need to make it more often.
So good!
Good morning!
Today I'm making a papaya bowl for breakfast with a little twist.
I added some coconut yogurt and it was really good.
I sprinkled some- sprinkled?
I drizzled some raw honey and enjoyed while watching some YouTube videos.
And now I'm getting ready because I'm meeting my friend Elina.
We're having lunch and catching up, and I'm really excited to see her.
I
am back home, back in the kitchen.
It was so lovely catching up with Elena.
She is just the sweetest.
She got me these stickers from her brand, Studio Sony.
And I am so excited to put these on my journal.
I mean, they are just so cute.
On my way back home, I bought some broccolini, and I'm gonna roast some chicken thighs in the oven with some lemon and garlic and
parsley, and since I bought a lot of sweet potatoes in the beginning of this week, I'm gonna make a sweet potato mash.
I feel like it's gonna pair well with this dish, and it's also super yummy.
Thank you!
Oh my goodness, the skin on the chicken is amazing.
I'm honestly so proud of this dish because I had this vision in my head, and somehow I was able to create this masterpiece.
Okay, I'm kidding, but I basically like TikTok-ed how to cook broccolini, how to cook sweet potato mash, and also with the chicken thighs, so I'm really
excited to dig in.
I think it's going to taste amazing, and Helge is here; he's gonna eat it with me.
I'm always a bit worried when I'm cooking chicken, but I think it's properly cooked.
Okay, this is very good.
This is gonna stay in the rotation.
Yeah!
Ah, I felt so good going out for a run, and the weather is amazing.
I was listening to a podcast, The Skinny Confidential Him and Her Show, and it's a podcast with Tony Robbins,
and wow, that man is just full of wisdom.
I actually own a book by him, Awakening the Giant Within or something, but I haven't read it.
I actually should because he is incredible.
For breakfast today, I'm gonna make avocado toast and scrambled eggs, but first I'm gonna go and take a shower.
Thank you.
I was trying to spice things up with the avocado toast
and also the scrambled eggs, but I added some honey and chili and lemon for more
flavor.
The scrambled eggs are very good with the tomatoes, basil, and parmesan.
Bye bye!
It's been a while since I made something with halloumi, so I thought we could make a little wrap today with some veggies
and tzatziki, even though we don't have everything to make tzatziki, but we'll just improvise with what we have, and it's probably going to be
super yummy.
I guess looks a lot better than mine.
Looks very good.
Cheers.
This is good.
I like it.
Halloumi is so good.
I think we need to go outside and enjoy this beautiful weather.
Maybe chill and read a book.
Oh my.
It's
dinner time, and tonight we are cooking one of my favorite home-cooked meals: steak with roasted potatoes, asparagus,
and peppercorn sauce.
It's funny because we never used to cook steak because we thought it would be too Complicated, but I'm telling you guys, it is actually very
simple once you learn it.
And honestly, this has become one of our go-to dishes during the weekends because you can easily mix up the vegetables or make a different
sauce, but the peppercorn is definitely our favorite.
The potatoes are so delicious.
I bought the ones that have like the purple skin.
I don't know, but these are incredible.
And also, the peppercorn sauce turned out so good.
I hope you guys enjoyed watching and maybe got some recipe inspiration.
Please let me know if you would like to see another video like this.
Thank you so much for watching, and I will see you next week.
Bye!